Coming in at number nine.
>> What?
>> What? What?
>> We're talking about my list. Nine. I'm
about to leave this [__] building.
I'm going Eigor number one. Flower boy
number two, then Chromacopia. Then Call
Me If You Get Lost, then Don't Tap the
Glass. Cherry Bomb next, then Wolf.
Bastard Goblin. Okay, you know what?
I'll start from the bottom.
>> Oh, okay. Coming in at number nine,
Flower Boy.
>> What?
>> What? We're talking about my list.
>> No. Whats? You're still wrong.
>> No, we're talking about my list. Number
eight is Don't Tap the Glass. Number
seven is Wolf.
>> Number six is Chromacopia.
>> Have you been drinking?
>> Five is Goblin. Four is Bastard. Three
is Cherry Bomb. Two is Call Me If You
Get Lost. Number one is Eigor.
I wasn't ready for that. [laughter] What
the I'm not.
This is old Charles coming out.
>> [laughter]
>> I thought you were grounded, more
center, not a troll as much.
>> No, this is not trolling. We It's very
ironic that on a Tyler the Creator
season where we are championing people
being themselves and speaking their
opinion, you guys are trying to make me
join the consensus. Oh, maybe I'm the
one that needs to grow.
>> Maybe I need to open my mind and just
let let
>> it be what it be. Like [__]
>> this is the DA speaking.